For You <3
nothing's going to change my love for
you you ought to know by now how much I
love you one thing you can be sure of
I'll never ask for more than your love
nothing's going to change my love for
you you ought to know by now how much I
love you the one might change my whole
life through but nothing's going to
change my love for nothing's going to
change my love for you you ought to know
by now how much I love you one thing you
can be sure oh I'll never ask for more
than your love nothing's going to change
my love for you you ought to know by now
how much I love you the one I change my
whole life through but's going to change
my love for
you